paksociety.com 2019-04-12

# Privacy Policy « Reading Section

We Started Paksociety in 2009, Our objective was to give users a clean and fast site with ultimate speed and quality stuff. During our journey we starts to provide direct downloading links, first ever in Pakistan. We are founder of introducing new trends in books website, We add scribd preview for the first time in a book website, and now almost all websites which you can termed as cop cats are using same technique to show books.  
**Advertisement**

Today we are at **No 1 Position** in our Pakistan related to books, Because we are not giving spams on our site, We are putting advertisement but in decent manner, We are updating old stuff with new one on regular basis. We can also termed as **No Dead Link Site**. Beside of this intro our users know about us very much.

The privacy of our visitors to **https://rspk.paksociety.com** is important to us.  
Privacy Policy for **https://rspk.paksociety.com**  
At **https://rspk.paksociety.com** , we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit https://rspk.paksociety.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

 **Log Files** As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons** ,We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on **https://rspk.paksociety.com** to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo targeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

 **DoubleClick DART cookies** We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>  
You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

We DO NOT host any Books on this website. All books found on our site are found freely available around the web on sites such as Facebook.com , mediafire.com Etc. We make no guarantees or promises in our service and take no liability for our users actions. We are not affiliated nor claim to be affiliated with any of the owners of book on our site. All content is copyright of their respective owners.

### Comments Posting Rules

1\. Comments will be moderated  
2\. Comments that are abusive, personal, incendiary or irrelevant cannot be published.  
3\. Please write complete sentences. Do not type comments in all capital letters.  
4\. We may remove hyperlinks within comments.  
5\. Please use a genuine email ID and provide your name, to avoid rejection.

The Books (Offline or Live) are and posted by the users of this website which are mostly from mediafire and Facebook. If you want to Remove some content from this website then immediately send an email to complaint[@]paksociety.com, We can delete the post and respond immediately.
